New York State Education Department Section 3020a Files, Panel Decisions 5741
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Education Department Section 3020a Files, Panel Decisions
1976-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Education Department
5741
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Panel decisions from labor agreements for the New York State Education Department Section 3020a
5699387
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5377: New York State Bureau of Industrial and Technical Education Records 5741: New York State Education Department Section 3020a Files, Panel Decisions 5780/166 PUBS: ILGWU Education Department Publications 6047: Archives Information File 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/002: NYSUT Vice President's Office files 6174/003: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services. Files 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files 6174/016: NYSUT Vice-President's Office Maria Neira. Files 6174/018: NYSUT Division of Research and Educational Services, Maria Neira Files 6366: Eric W. Lawson Arbitration Files
School employees -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- State government employees -- New York (State); University of the State of New York.
5699387
- 1976 unnumbered to 1979 unnumbered. (Box 1)
  - State of NY School District Cases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 416, 451, 455, 461, 480 and unnumbered, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nos. 375 - 496, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nos. 506 - 555, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - State of NY State Education Department Office of Employer-Employee Relations, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 523 - 615, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nos. 616 - 718, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - State of NY State Education Department, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NY State Education Department, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1980 #458-714 to 1981 #886-1013. (Box 2)
  - Nos. 458 - 717, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - State of NY State Education Department, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Nos. 715 - 859, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The State of NY State Education Department, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - State of NY Department of Education, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 486 - 819, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Nos. 821 - 885, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Nos. 886 - 1013, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1981 unnumbered to 1983 #1019-1174. (Box 3)
  - The State of NY, The State Education Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State of NY, State Education Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State University of NY, State Education Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Nos. 656 - 928, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nos. 962 - 1054, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 1055 - 1266 and Unnumbered, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The University of the State of NY, The State Education Department, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Nos. 681 - 988, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Nos. 1019 - 1177, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 1983 #1183-1355 to 1985 #1531-1614. (Box 4)
  - Nos. 1183 - 1355, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State of New York, The State Department of Education, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State of New York, State Department of Education, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The University of the State of New York, The State Education Department, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nos. 579 - 1309, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 1310 - 1355, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Nos. 1379 - 1440, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nos. 1012 - 1421, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nos. 1424 - 1524, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nos. 1531 - 1614, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 1985 unnumbered to 1987 unnumbered. (Box 5)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nos. 1411 - 1741, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nos. 1494 - 1741, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - State of New York, The State Education Department, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nos. 1539 - 1877, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 1988 #1526a-unnumbered to 1990 #2116-2146 & unnumbered. (Box 6)
  - Nos. 1526a - 1830, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nos. 1855 - 1979, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The University of the State of New York, The State Education Department, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nos. 1543 - 1935, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Nos. 1946 - 1995, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Nos. 2001 - 2102, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - State of New York, State Education Department, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nos. 1837 - 2110, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Nos. 2116 - 2146 and Unnumbered, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)